<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-01-20T13:43:52-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Hera Global Tech</title><subtitle>You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document  head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site  description.
</subtitle><author><name>Brady Sheehan</name></author><entry><title type="html">News</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/updates/2017/12/16/updates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="News" /><published>2017-12-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/updates/2017/12/16/updates</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/updates/2017/12/16/updates/"></content><author><name>Brady Sheehan</name></author><category term="updates" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Introducing ‘Autonomous’</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/services/2017/09/21/services-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing 'Autonomous'" /><published>2017-09-21T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-09-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/services/2017/09/21/services-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/services/2017/09/21/services-1/">&lt;p&gt;When one is scared or afraid, the body automatically responds with an increase in heart rate, pulse, and respiration, all functioning to tell the brain they are in danger. Known as the fight or flight response, this condition is universal across all humans. Autonomous, worn inconspicuously as a patch on the body, monitors these physiologic responses in real time. When fight or flight conditions present, Autonomous communicates the wearer’s location to an identified support group that help is needed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brady Sheehan</name></author><category term="services" /><summary type="html">When one is scared or afraid, the body automatically responds with an increase in heart rate, pulse, and respiration, all functioning to tell the brain they are in danger. Known as the fight or flight response, this condition is universal across all humans. Autonomous, worn inconspicuously as a patch on the body, monitors these physiologic responses in real time. When fight or flight conditions present, Autonomous communicates the wearer’s location to an identified support group that help is needed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our Team</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/team/2017/08/21/team/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our Team" /><published>2017-08-21T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-08-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/team/2017/08/21/team</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/team/2017/08/21/team/">&lt;p&gt;The team at Hera Global Tech comes with diverse professional backgrounds, representing a complementary mix of design, technology, healthcare and research professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poorvi Mathur is a design manager with expertise in design thinking, research and innovation, and a keen interest in social impact. She conceptualized Autonomous as a response to the brutal gang rape of Jyoti Sharma, a young girl in Delhi in 2012. Having lived in India and the USA, she brings in valuable understanding of the problem in a global context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elizabeth M. La Rue is a world and culture explorer who focuses on social dynamics, customs, and communication patterns. She is an expert in healthcare informatics curriculum design and research processes. Experiences from living in Sub-Saharan Africa and the Western World motivate her to be an advocate for equal education and social responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brady Sheehan is a software engineer with a strong background in mathematics. His experience comes from multiple years of research in low-level computer vision, both within industry and academia. He enjoys applying mathematical models to solve problems in a wide range of domains with the ultimate goal of helping people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jarad Prinkey is a research bioengineer with strong skills in embedded technology and prototype electronics, software and hardware. He likes to use new and old technology to design biosensor systems for the measurement of everything from the pressure profile of someone sitting in a chair to the acceleration of a football helmet during a simulated head-to-head tackle. He enjoys using off the shelf technology in new and innovative ways.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brady Sheehan</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">The team at Hera Global Tech comes with diverse professional backgrounds, representing a complementary mix of design, technology, healthcare and research professionals.</summary></entry></feed>